Dead in the Water is a thriller, tv movie film directed by Sheldon Wilson.
The Nereus is a fifty-year-old Ice Breaker, salvaged by an
idealistic crew on a mission to catch illegal fisherman.
On chase, the crew find themselves well off-course and bearing down on a
body mysteriously floating in the middle of the Devil’s Sea.
Superstitious or not, the team soon discovers they’ve rescued a
deadly creature feeding on the lifeless body.
Their new mission—kill or be killed and preferably before they hit land.
Dana, played by Nikohl Boosheri.
Sparks, played by Christia Visser.
Erika, played by Tanya van Graan.
Michelle, played by Amy Louise Wilson.
Stranger, played by Brandon Auret.
Kat, played by Nicole Fortuin.
Black Water is an American action thriller film directed by Pasha Patriki.
It stars Jean-Claude Van Damme and Dolph Lundgren in their fifth collaboration,
specifically the second time they appear as on-screen allies.
The film was released direct-to-video in the US on May 25, 2018.
The film explores themes of ship, expedition,
stranger, pacific  ocean, wreckage.
The tone is intense.